Vladimir Parkhomenko Kramatorsk, Ukraine 84200 +38(050) 800-26-87 obhodny@gmail.com

Ī

OBJECTIVE

To obtain a remote position Middle Python Developer

SUMMARY OF QUALIFICATIONS:

Experienced Information Technology Professional, with work experience of 6 years Work well independently, or in a group setting providing.

Capable of working with a variety of technology and software solutions, and managing databases. In-depth knowledge and understanding of numerous software packages and technologies. Excellent communication and presentation capabilities.

EDUCATION:

Donbass State Mechanical Engineering Academy Kramatorsk, Ukraine

Bachelor's Degree

Major: Information Technology **GPA: 75** of a maximum 95

Donbass State Mechanical Engineering Academy Kramatorsk, Ukraine

Computer Systems Engineer

Major: Information Technology

GPA: 80 of a maximum 95

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE:

Qencode, (5/2018 - Present) **Web Developer**, **Python Developer**

The most effective cloud video transcoding solution in the market. My responsibility is web development. The responsibility is to develop modules, models and controllers. Development of both front-end and back-end scripts. Database modeling. Using the REST API, the integration of the payment system, the development of the billing system and SDK (Python) etc.

AlterEgo, Kramatorsk, Ukraine Middle Python Developer

(11/2014 – Present)

My responsibility is Python and web programming Development of modules, models, scripts, designing databases. API development and use of APIs such as awsamazon, google, stripe, etc

AlterEgo, Kramatorsk, Ukraine **Layout desidner**

(3/2014 - 10/2014)

Making pages and integration into the system. Development of front-end scripts on JavaScript

PROFESSIONAL SKILS:

Knowledgeable

Operation Systems: GNU/Linux(Debian, CentOS)

Programming Language: Python

WebDevelopment:
PHP, JavaScript, SQL, HTML, CSS, JSON,

XML. REST

FrameWork & Librare:
Django, Codeigniter, AngularJS, jQery,

WordPress

Modeling:

Databases:
MySQL

Networking:
HTTP, REST

UVCS: GIT, SVN

Basic

Operation System: Windows

Programming Language:
C, C++, Go, JAVA, C#

WebDevelopment:
TypeScript, Ajax
FrameWork & Librare:
Flask Angular 4

FrameWork & Librare:Databases:Flask, Angular 4Postgresgl, Redis

Networking:

Testing:
Unit Testing

Study

Machine deep learning: Tensorflow, Keras

PROJECTS:

Stagevids, Qencode

LANGUAGES:

- Ukrainian (native)
- Russian (native)
- English (basic)

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION & LINKS:

LinkedIn:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/vladimirparkhomenko/

Skype:

Uladimir_vladimirr